{"data":[{"question":"________ occasions for congratulations.","a":"Birthdays that usually considered","b":"Usually considering birthdays","c":"Birthdays are usually considered","d":"That considered birthdays usually","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Passive voice: S + TO BE + PP.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Forty-niners ________ to California for gold in 1848.","a":"rushed","b":"are rushed","c":"have rushed","d":"rushing","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple past tense: Use the Simple Past to express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past (in 1848).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"In order for people to work together effectively, they need ________ Each other's needs.","a":"to be sensitive to","b":"is sensitive for","c":"sensitivity","d":"sensitive","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Need to be\/to Verb.\u00a0\n- Sensitive to sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"It is good form to use the name of the person ________.","a":"who are greeting","b":"you are greeting","c":"which you are greeting","d":"greeting for you","answer":"2","explain":"\nRelative clause: \n+ Who: replaces person in subject.\u00a0\n+ Whom: replaces person in object.\u00a0\n+ Which: replaces for things.\u00a0\n- This case, replaced person is object- whom, however, whom is omitted.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"________ the promotion of health and to helping people avoid injury and disease.","a":"To commit the Red Cross","b":"The Red Cross to commit","c":"Committed to the Red Cross is","d":"The Red Cross is committed to","answer":"4","explain":"\n- To be committed to do sth\/sth.\n- Narrative sentence: S + V + O.\n- \"the promotion of health and to helping people avoid injury and disease\" is object- in ............. must be: S +V.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"People usually can get a sufficient amount of the calcium their bodies ________ from the food they consume.","a":"need","b":"needs","c":"needing","d":"to need","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Narrative sentence: S + V + O.\u00a0\n- People: plural subject- need.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"It is possible ________ may assist some trees in saving water in the winter.","a":"the leaves are lost","b":"when leaves have lost","c":"that the loss of leaves","d":"to lose leaves","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Structure: It's adj\/ noun that+ clause.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Hollywood, the heart of America's motion picture industry, ________ of Los Angeles a century ago.","a":"was only a quiet suburb","b":"only quiet suburb was","c":"quiet suburb only was","d":"suburb was quiet only","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Narrative sentence: S + V + O.\u00a0\n- Use a pair of commas in the middle of a sentence to set off clauses, phrases, and words that are not essential to the meaning of the sentence= main clause is: Hollywood + S + O (was only a quiet suburb).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Kitchen appliances called blenders became ________ in the 1930s, when Stephen J. Poplawski developed a machine that excelled at making his favorite drink.","a":"establish","b":"establishing","c":"established","d":"which establish","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Get\/become established: to start feeling happy, confident, and successful in a new job or place.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Built at the beginning of the century, the Library of Congress houses one of the largest ________ collections of books in the world.","a":"and fine","b":"and finest","c":"or finest","d":"yet fine","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Parallel structure: structure before and after \"and\" must be parallel.\u00a0\nSuperlative form of adjective\/adverb: \n+ Short adj: The + adj\/adv +est.\u00a0\n+ Long adj: The + most + adj\/adv.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"}]}